Guide to the Howard Zinn Papers TAM.542
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Writings, 1901-2009; 445627
  - Books: A People's History of American Empire, 2004-2008; cuid15545; 445719 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Books: A People's History of the United States, 1981, 1993, 1994, undated; cuid15546; 445720 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Books: A People's History of the United States - Audio, 1998-2003; cuid15547; 445721 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Books: A People's History of the United States - Editor's Proof (I), [1980]; cuid15548; 445722 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Books: A People's History of the United States - Editor's Proof (II), [1980]; cuid15549; 445723 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Books: A People's History of the United States - Editor's Proof (III), [1980]; cuid15550; 445724 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Books: A People's History of the United States - Editor's Proof (IV), [1980]; cuid15551; 445725 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Books: A People's History of the United States - Editor's Proof (V), [1980]; cuid15552; 445726 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Books: A People's History of the United States - Fragments, Notes and Resource Material for Chapter "The Coming Revolt of the Guards", 1973-1978, undated; cuid15553; 445727 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Books: A People's History of the United States - Proposed Changes / Corrections, 1989-2008, undated; cuid15554; 445728 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Books: A People's History of the United States - Reviews, 1979-Apr 1980; cuid15555; 445729 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Books: A People's History of the United States - Reviews, May 1980-Aug 1980; cuid15556; 445730 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Books: A People's History of the United States - Reviews, Oct 1980-Dec 1980; cuid15557; 445731 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Books: A People's History of the United States - Reviews, 1981-1987, 1990-1996; cuid15558; 445734 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Books: A People's History of the United States - Reviews, undated; cuid15559; 445754 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Books: A People's History of the United States - Reviews - Handlin, Oscar (The American Scholar, 1981), and Responses, cuid15560; 445755 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Books: A People's History of the United States - Reviews - Kazin, Michael (Dissent, Spring 2004) and Responses, 2004, 2007; cuid15561; 445756 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Books: A People's History of the United States - Student Project to Design Book Jacket, undated; cuid15562; 445757 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Books: A People's History of the United States - "A Textual-Contextual Analysis of Howard Zinn's A People's History of the United States" (student paper), 1981; cuid15563; 445758 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Books: A People's History of the United States - Twentieth Anniversary Edition, 1999-2000; cuid15564; 445759 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Books: A People's History of the United States - Various Adaptations (Echoes: A People's History, a multi-media presentation), 1991-1994; cuid15565; 445760 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Books: A People's History of the United States - Various Adaptations (proposed abridgements including a young people's edition), 1991-1994, 1999; cuid15566; 445761 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Books: A People's History of the United States - Various Adaptations (proposed animation projects), 2005-2008; cuid15567; 445762 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Books: A People's History of the United States - Various Adaptations and Formats (proposed website), 1999; cuid15568; 445763 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Books: A People's History of the United States - Various Adaptations and Formats (various other proposals), 1995-1999, 2009, undated; cuid15569; 445764 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Books: The Politics of History, 1967-1970, 1989; cuid15570; 445765 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Books: The Politics of History (Second Edition), 1989-1990; cuid15571; 445766 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Books: The Politics of History - Editor's Proof (I), [1970]; cuid15572; 445767 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Books: The Politics of History - Editor's Proof (II), [1970]; cuid15573; 445768 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Books: The Politics of History - Editor's Proof (III), [1970]; cuid15574; 445769 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Books: The Politics of History - Editor's Proof (IV), [1970]; cuid15575; 445770 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Books: The Politics of History - Reviews, 1970-1975; cuid15576; 445771 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Books: Postwar America: 1945-1971, 1966-1975; cuid15577; 445772 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Books: Postwar America: 1945-1971 - Reviews, 1973-1974, undated; cuid15578; 445773 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Books: Potential Book of Essays on Abolishing War, with Gino Strada (including email from Arundhati Roy), 2005-2006; cuid15579; 445774 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Books: Potential Book of Essays on Abolishing War, with Gino Strada (including fax messages and essay from Nadine Gordimer; also email from Cindy Sheehan), 1997-2006, undated; cuid15580; 445775 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Books: A Power That Governments Cannot Suppress, 2005-2008; cuid15581; 445776 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Books: A Power That Governments Cannot Suppress - Reviews, 2007-2008; cuid15582; 445777 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Books: The Power of Nonviolence, [2002]; cuid15583; 445778 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Books: The Rule of Law (Zinn was a contributor) - Review, 1971; cuid15584; 445779 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Books: SNCC: The New Abolitionists, [1964]; cuid15585; 445780 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Books: SNCC: The New Abolitionists - Reviews, 1964-1965; cuid15586; 445781 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Books: The Southern Mystique, 1958-1964, undated; cuid15587; 445782 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Books: The Southern Mystique - Correspondence, 1962-1965; cuid15588; 445783 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Books: The Southern Mystique - Reviews, 1964-1968, undated; cuid15589; 445784 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Books: Terrorism and War, 2003-2005; cuid15590; 445785 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Books: Three Plays: The Political Theater of Howard Zinn, 2009, undated; cuid15591; 445801 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Books: Three Strikes, 2001; cuid15592; 445802 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Books: The Twentieth Century: A People's History, 1981-1983, 2003; cuid15593; 445803 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Books: The Twentieth Century: A People's History - Review, 1985; cuid15594; 445805 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Books: Uncommon Sense, 2007, 2008; cuid15595; 445806 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Books: Vietnam: The Logic of Withdrawal, 1966-1968; cuid15596; 445807 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Books: Vietnam: The Logic of Withdrawal, [1967]; cuid15597; 445808 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Books: Vietnam: The Logic of Withdrawal - Reviews, 1967-1968; cuid15598; 445809 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Books: Vietnam: The Logic of Withdrawal - Reader Actions (includes letters from Edward M. Kennedy and from Edward W. Brooke), 1967; cuid15599; 445810 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Books: Voices of a People's History of the United States, 2004-2005, undated; cuid15600; 445811 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Books: You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train, 1992-1995, [2002]; cuid15601; 445812 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Books: You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train - Editor's Proof (I), [1994]; cuid15602; 445813 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Books: You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train - Editor's Proof (II), [1994]; cuid15603; 445814 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Books: You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train - Reviews, 1994-1996; cuid15604; 445815 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Books: A Young People's History of the United States, 2007, 2009; cuid15605; 445816 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Books: The Zinn Reader, 1996-2001; cuid15606; 445817 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Dissertation: "Conscience of the Jazz Age: LaGuardia in Congress" (personal hand-written card from Mrs. Marie LaGuardia enclosed), 1959, undated; cuid15607; 445818 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Drafts and Fragments, undated; cuid15608; 445819 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Eulogies: Luria, Salvador (includes correspondence and memorial program), 1991; cuid15609; 445820 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Letters to the Editor, 1963-2008; cuid15610; 445821 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Liner Notes: Fellow Workers (Ani DiFranco), 1999; cuid15611; 445822 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Films: "Revolution" (unproduced adaptation of A People's History of the United States, script by Howard Fast), 2000-2002; cuid15612; 445823 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Films: You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train - Correspondence, 2003-2005; cuid15613; 445824 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Films: You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train - Press, 2003-2004, undated; cuid15614; 445825 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Films: You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train - Reviews, 2004; cuid15615; 445826 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Films: You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train - Screenings, 2004-2006, undated; cuid15616; 445827 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Pamphlets: Columbus, the Indians, and Human Progress 1492-1992, cuid15617; 445828 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Pamphlets: Hiroshima: Breaking the Silence, 1995; cuid15618; 445829 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Pamphlets: Power, History and Warfare, 1991-1992; cuid15619; 445830 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Pamphlets: Times Square, undated; cuid15620; 445831 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Plays: As the World Turns - Productions, Jan 2001-Apr 2001, undated; cuid15621; 445833 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Plays: As the World Turns - Script (also includes notes and fragments), undated; cuid15622; 445834 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Background, 2001, 2003, 2006; cuid15623; 445836 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Correspondence, 1985-1986, 2007-2009, undated; cuid15624; 445837 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Notes, undated; cuid15625; 445838 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Productions (New York), 1985, undated; cuid15626; 445839 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Productions (White Barn Theater, Westport CT), 1986, undated; cuid15627; 445840 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Productions (unknown), undated; cuid15628; 445841 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Reviews, 1986, 2009; cuid15629; 445842 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Scripts (Daughter of Venus) (I), 2006; cuid15630; 445843 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Scripts (Daughter of Venus) (II), 2006; cuid15631; 445844 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Scripts (Daughter of Venus) (III), 2006; cuid15632; 445845 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Scripts (Daughter of Venus) (IV), 2006; cuid15633; 445846 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Scripts (Daughter of Venus), undated; cuid15634; 445847 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Scripts (Unsafe Distances) (I), undated; cuid15635; 445848 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Scripts (Unsafe Distances) (II), undated; cuid15636; 445849 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Scripts (Unsafe Distances) (III), undated; cuid15637; 445850 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Plays: Emma - Adaptations - Movie Script and Treatment, undated; cuid15638; 445851 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Plays: Emma - Adaptations - Opera (cello), 2005; cuid15639; 445852 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Plays: Emma - Adaptations - Opera (clarinet), 2005; cuid15640; 445853 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Plays: Emma - Adaptations - Opera (general), 2004-2005, undated; cuid15641; 445854 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Plays: Emma - Adaptations - Opera (percussion), 2005; cuid15642; 445855 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Plays: Emma - Adaptations - Opera (piano), 2005; cuid15643; 445856 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Plays: Emma - Adaptations - Opera (piano vocal score), 2005; cuid15644; 445857 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Plays: Emma - Adaptations - Opera (trumpet), 2005; cuid15645; 445858 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Plays: Emma - Adaptations - Opera (violin), 2005; cuid15646; 445859 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Plays: Emma - Adaptations - Rebel in Paradise, 1985-1987, undated; cuid15647; 445860 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Plays: Emma - Adaptations - Rebel in Paradise (poster), [1987]; cuid15648; 445861 (Flat-file-folder 7)
  - Plays: Emma - Adaptations - Red Emma, 1995, undated; cuid15649; 445862 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Plays: Emma - Background - Almeda Sperry, 1975-1976, undated; cuid15650; 445863 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Plays: Emma - Background - Exile Letters, undated; cuid15651; 445864 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Plays: Emma - Background - General, 1981, 1989-1990, 1993, undated; cuid15652; 445865 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Plays: Emma - Background - Raw Data, 1983, 1985, undated; cuid15653; 445866 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Plays: Emma - Background - Slide Photos, undated; cuid15654; 445867 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Plays: Emma - Background - The True Story of the Assassination of President McKinley at Buffalo by Richard H. Barry, 1901; cuid15655; 445868 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Plays: Emma - Correspondence - General, 1976-1991, undated; cuid15656; 445869 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Plays: Emma - Final Draft Disk (screenwriting software), 2001; cuid15657; 445870 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Plays: Emma - Introduction, undated; cuid15658; 445871 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Plays: Emma - Music, 2005, undated; cuid15659; 445872 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Plays: Emma - Poster, undated; cuid15660; 445873 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Plays: Emma - Productions (Bilbao), 2009; cuid15661; 445874 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Plays: Emma - Productions (Bordeaux), 2009; cuid15662; 445875 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Plays: Emma - Productions (Boston), 1977, undated; cuid15663; 445876 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Plays: Emma - Productions (Boston) - Correspondence, 1977-1978, undated; cuid15664; 445877 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Plays: Emma - Productions (Japan), 1990-1991, 2010, undated; cuid15665; 445878 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Plays: Emma - Productions (Japan), undated; cuid15666; 445879 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Plays: Emma - Productions (Japan) - Poster, undated; cuid15667; 445880 (Flat-file-folder 7)
  - Plays: Emma - Productions (New York 1986), 1985-1986, undated; cuid15668; 445881 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Plays: Emma - Productions (various), 1986, 1994-2009, undated; cuid15669; 445882 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Plays: Emma - Productions (Woodstock), 2004; cuid15670; 445883 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Plays: Emma - Readings (Suffolk), 2008; cuid15671; 445884 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Plays: Emma - Related Works - E.G. a Musical Portrait of Emma Goldman, 1986, 1994; cuid15672; 445885 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Plays: Emma - Reviews (Boston), 1976-1977; cuid15673; 445886 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Plays: Emma - Reviews (London), 1987; cuid15674; 445887 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Plays: Emma - Reviews (New York), 1986; cuid15675; 445888 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Plays: Emma - Reviews (South End Press), 2001, 2003-2005, undated; cuid15676; 445890 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Plays: Emma - Reviews (various), 1976, 1979, 1994, undated; cuid15677; 445891 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Plays: Emma - Scripts, undated; cuid15678; 445892 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Plays: Emma - Scripts (French), undated; cuid15679; 445893 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Plays: Emma - Scripts (Japanese), 1990, undated; cuid15680; 445894 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Plays: Emma - Scripts ("later"), undated; cuid15681; 445895 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Plays: Emma - Scripts (London), undated; cuid15682; 445896 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Plays: Emma - Scripts - "New York 1986 Script", cuid15683; 445897 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Plays: Emma - Scripts - "New York Long Script (to 1917)", undated; cuid15684; 445898 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Plays: Emma - Scripts - Original, undated; cuid15685; 445899 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Background (Bakunin), undated; cuid15686; 445900 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Background (Capital), 1942, undated; cuid15687; 445901 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Background (Lassalle), undated; cuid15688; 445902 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Background (Marx biography), 1984-1987, 1997, undated; cuid15689; 445903 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Background (raw data), undated; cuid15690; 445904 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - General, 1993, 1999-2003, undated; cuid15691; 445905 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Notes, undated; cuid15692; 445906 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Productions (Boston), 2000; cuid15693; 445907 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Productions (Cuba), 2004-2006; cuid15694; 445908 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Productions (Italy), 2007-2009; cuid15695; 445909 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Productions (Japan), 2002, undated; cuid15696; 445910 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Productions (Tampa), 1998-2000, undated; cuid15697; 445911 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Productions (various, abroad), 1993, 1999-2009, undated; cuid15698; 445912 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Productions (various, domestic), 1993-2005; cuid15699; 445913 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Productions (various, domestic), 2006-2009, undated; cuid15700; 445914 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Reviews (productions), 1999-2006, undated; cuid15701; 445915 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Reviews (South End Press), 1999-2001, undated; cuid15702; 445916 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Scripts, Sep 1988; cuid15703; 445917 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Scripts, Jan 1989; cuid15704; 445918 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Scripts, Jun 1998; cuid15705; 445919 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Scripts (I), undated; cuid15706; 445920 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Scripts (II), undated; cuid15707; 445921 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Uncorrected Galley Proof of Marx in Soho: A Play on History (South End Press), 1998; cuid15708; 445922 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Readings: "The People Speak" - Sundance, Jan 2009; cuid15709; 445923 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Readings: "The People Speak" - Voices of Dissent, [2008]; cuid15710; 445924 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Readings: A People's History of the United States - Harper Collins Millionth Copy Event, 2002, 2003, undated; cuid15711; 445925 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Readings: A People's History of the United States - Harper Collins Millionth Copy Event (correspondence), 2002, 2003, undated; cuid15712; 445926 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - 92nd Street Y, May 2009; cuid15713; 445937 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Baltimore, Nov 2009; cuid15714; 445938 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Berkeley, Nov 2006, undated; cuid15715; 445939 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Boston, 2004, undated; cuid15716; 445940 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Boulder, 2008, undated; cuid15717; 445941 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Cooper Union, 2006; cuid15718; 445942 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Cooper Union, May 2007; cuid15719; 445943 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Denver, Oct 2007; cuid15720; 445944 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Harlem, Dec 2005; cuid15721; 445945 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Lannan Foundation, Stanta Fe, New Mexico, 2006, undated; cuid15722; 445946 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Los Angeles, 2005, undated; cuid15723; 445947 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Los Angeles, 2006, undated; cuid15724; 445948 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Minnesota, 2009; cuid15725; 445949 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - New York, 2006; cuid15726; 445950 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - New York Pubic Lilbrary, Sep 2005; cuid15727; 445951 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - New York Small Presses, undated; cuid15728; 445952 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - New York Society for Ethical Culture, 2004; cuid15729; 445953 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Pasadena, 2007; cuid15730; 445954 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Provincetown, 2007; cuid15731; 445955 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Raw Material, 2001-2003, undated; cuid15732; 445956 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Raw Material, undated; cuid15733; 445957 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Recordings, 2005; cuid15734; 445959 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Reviews, 2005; cuid15735; 445960 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - San Francisco, 2009; cuid15736; 445961 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Seattle, undated; cuid15737; 445962 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Vassar College, 2005; cuid15738; 445963 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Washington D.C., 2005; cuid15739; 445964 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Screenplays: "Purgatory River", 2008; cuid15740; 445965 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Screenplays: "Purgatory River" - Working Title, "A Western Story", Oct 1997; cuid15741; 445966 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Screenplays: "Purgatory River" - Working Title, "A Western Story", Oct 1997-Nov 1997; cuid15742; 445967 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Special Report: Albany, A Study in National Responsibility, 1962; cuid15743; 445968 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Speeches: "Academic Freedom: Collaboration and Resistance" The 23rd T.B.Davis Memorial Lecture, University of Cape Town, South Africa, 1982; cuid15744; 445969 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Speeches: Christopher Columbus, 1991-1992; cuid15745; 445970 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Speeches: Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1989, 1991-1994; cuid15746; 445972 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Speeches: France in 2003, 2003-2004; cuid15747; 445973 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Speeches: "Just War" (Rome), [2003]; cuid15748; 445974 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Speeches: Various, [1957], 1985, 1986, 2005-2009; cuid15749; 445975 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Speeches: Vietnam War, 1966-1971, undated; cuid15750; 445977 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Tapings: "The People Speak" - Actor Brochure, 2007-2008; cuid15751; 445978 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Tapings: "The People Speak" - Audience Reactions, 2005, undated; cuid15752; 445979 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Tapings: "The People Speak" - Boston, Jan 2009; cuid15753; 445980 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Tapings: "The People Speak" - Press, 2007-2008; cuid15754; 445982 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Tapings: "The People Speak" - Reviews, 2008, undated; cuid15755; 445983 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Television: The People Speak - Press, 2009; cuid15756; 445990 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Television: "The People Speak" - Script (green script), Jan 2007; cuid15757; 445993 (Box 16, Folder 33)